在印第安纳州时
Back in Indiana,
盥洗室总是一个很私人的地方
the bathroom was always a private place.
但因为我现在在纽约
But now that I live in New York,
一如纽约的其他事物一样 于是也很拥挤
like everything else, it's crowded.
吮指的快乐是什么 鸡肉?
What's finger-lickin', chicken?
没什么 大屁股
Nothin' much, butt.
我只是认为这押韵多了
That rhymed more in my head.
但是我觉得还不错啊
But I'm okay with it.
盥洗室确实成为了我和克洛伊
The bathroom's actually become a place
交流八卦的地方
where Chloe and I download and catch up.
我想去美黑下
I'm just about to give myself a Brazilian.
你想先试试吗?
Want me to do you first?
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
你确定吗 阿朱?
You sure, June?
今年都2013年啦 降低下线咯
It's 2013. Lower the deck.
# 我不完美 我也不打小报告 #
I'm not perfect, I'm no snitch
# 但是我可以告诉你 #
but I can tell you
# 她是一个... #
She's a...
# 吧哒哒哒哒吧 吧哒吧 #
Ba-Da-Da-Da-Da-Ba, ba-Da-Ba
23号公寓第二季第十七集 占用中
精心修饰给谁看呢?
So, who's the special grooming for?
班吉b结束了洛杉矶的导演工作
Benjamin's back from his directing gig in L.A.
在一部名叫"艾格尼丝"的电影里
He made Joseph Gordon-Levitt kiss Melissa Mccarthy
他安排约瑟夫・高登莱维特去亲梅丽莎・麦卡锡
in a movie I'm really looking forward to seeing
我非常想去看呢
called "Agnes."
听起来很棒
Sounds great.
没错 在他飞回澳大利亚前
Yeah. Now he's directing James in some big new Commercial
他负责给詹姆斯的广告做导演
before he goes to australia.
要知道 这会是迄今我俩共度
You know, this is gonna be the longest amount of time
最漫长的时光了
we've actually ever spent together.
噢! 好棒!
Ooh! That's exciting!
我把他的地位提升到男友圈的首位
Yeah. I bumped him up to number one on my guy rotation.
二号到六号只好在我们翻云覆雨的时候
Numbers two through six are just gonna have to wait
默默等候了
while he puts his dingo in my baby.
克洛伊 你有没有和班吉b讲过男友圈 ?
Chloe, did you tell Benjamin about your rotation?
没有 为什么?
No. Why?
因为不是所有人都会有
Uh, because that's not just something that everyone has.
那每个人都该试试 很不错
Well, everyone should. It's awesome.
这是最完美的状况
It's the perfect situation.
没有输家 每个人都是赢家
Nobody loses. Everybody wins.
不是的 有个人输了
No, one person loses-- The person who thinks
他还以为女友钟情他一个呢
that they're dating someone Exclusively
却发现事实并非如此
and then finds out that's not the case.
就像我在七年级时和艾伦・德迈亚约会
Like me in seventh grade when I was dating Aaron demayo.
他是一名摔跤手 而我是一个平凡的女孩
He was a wrestler, and I was a mat maid--
大家都觉得我不是真正的啦啦队长
Which people don't think is a real cheerleader
因为我们连制服都没有
because we didn't have uniforms,
只能找衣柜里带紫色的衣服穿 权当制服
we just wore whatever shade of purple we had in our closet.
总之 当我发现艾伦还和特瑞沙・费雪约会时
Anyway, I was heartbroken when I found out
我伤心透了
that Aaron was also seeing Theresa Fisher.
难道告诉班吉b我有男友圈
Ugh. Is telling Benjamin about my guy rotation
是唯一能够让你停止叨叨的方法吗?
the only way I'm gonna get you to stop with the jibber-jabber?
是的
It is.
好吧 愿上帝帮助我
Fine. But so help me god,
如果我再听到一点叽叽 甚至一点喳喳
if I hear one jibber or even a piece of jabber,
我就会强行给你上美黑蜡
I will forcibly wax you. Mm.
很漂亮的盥洗室 那这广告是关于什么产品?
Sweet bathroom. What's this commercial for, anyway?
毛巾? 肥皂? 喷头?
Towels? Soap? Shower heads?
太阳眼镜
Sunglasses.
太酷了 我会看看的
Awesome. I'm watching.
啊 实际上 你不可能会看到
Ah, you won't be able to watch, actually.
这则广告只在日本播出
It's Only gonna air in Japan.
自从三个打扮成凯蒂猫的女孩
James is Huge there
注: 该片由詹姆斯出演
在"校园蓝调"的京都首映式里
ever since Three girls dressed as hello Kitty
被踩踏致死后
were trampled to death
詹姆斯在日本就声名赫赫了
at the "Varsity Blues" premiere in Kyoto.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 你自己?
Hey yourself?
我同时和另外五个男人约会
I'm dating five other guys.
我的男友圈里已经有六位男人了
I've got six guys in my rotation.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
我同时和另外五个女人约会
I'm dating five other girls,
但是我们把它称为"情人环"
except we call it a "Cycle."
噢 我的天 真有趣
Oh, my God. That is so funny.
澳大利人对所有事情都有不同的词语
Australians have different words for everything.
确实 和六个人约会难道不是最棒的吗?
We do. Isn't dating six people the best?
因为五个无法令人满足...
Because five is unsatisfying...
应付七个人又精力不够
and seven allows no time to recoup.
我才想起我为什么喜欢你
I just remembered why I like you.
- 你是那么的... - 性感?
- You are so... - hot?
我想说的是"放荡"
I was gonna say "Slutty."
我喜欢拍摄工作的第一天
Love the first day of production.
整组的人员都会喜爱我 尊重我
A whole new crew to love and respect me.
你知道我最喜爱的是哪部分吗?
You know what my favorite part is?
工具腰带吗?
All the tool belts?
不是
No.
首天的开机演说
First day of production speech.
我向全组人介绍自己
I introduce myself to the crew,
说一些鼓舞人心的话
say a few inspirational words,
记下一两个姓名 彰显我的平易近人
learn two of their names to show how accessible I am,
然后休息 沉湎于他们的钦佩中
then sit back and bask in their admiration.
这些好比燃料 让我动力十足
It's my fuel. Keeps me running.
- 每天我都能够从你那学到东西 - 嗯
- Every day, I learn from you. - Mm.
好的 大家!
All right, everyone!
我是班吉b・拉夫特 你们的导演
Um, I'm Benjamin Lovett, your director.
在我们开工之前我想要说几句
Just wanna say a few words before we start.
我知道你们中的某些人正在想
Now I know some of you may be wondering
为什么要在盥洗室里拍太阳眼镜广告
why we're doing a commercial for sunglasses in a bathroom.
特别是你俩 乔尔和米奇
Especially you, Joel, Mikey.
两个名字
Two names.
但盥洗室里度过的时光多么漫长
But so much of life happens in bathrooms,
许许多多亲密无间 意义非凡的时刻
so many intimate and important moments.
想一想...
Think about it--
什么时候最不设防?
When are you most vulnerable?
当你赤身裸体
When you're naked.
在哪里你总是赤身裸体?
And where are you most naked?
在盥洗室里
In the bathroom.
嗯
Mm.
一丝不挂... 很性感
And being naked... is sexy,
太阳眼镜... 也很性感
and sunglasses... are sexy.
所以我们要让盥洗室... 性感起来...
So we're gonna make this bathroom... sexy...
迷蒙起来...
and steamy...
湿气氤氲
and wet.
因为盥洗室就等于性感...
Because bathrooms equals sexy...
等于太阳眼镜
equals sunglasses.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
我不能接着说
I can't follow that.
一天不能有两个...
You can't have two...
鼓舞人心的首日开机演说
Inspiring first day of production speeches.
这个畜生篡取了我的权利
The S.O.B. usurped me.
他"彗星美人"了你
He "All about Eve'd" you.
什么?
What?
噢 抱歉 他"广告女郎"了你
Oh. Sorry. He "Showgirl'd" you.
他讲得比你好
He did better than you did.
啊
Uhh.
嘿 我真的喜欢你的演说
Hey. I really liked your speech.
噢? 哪一部分?
Oh, yeah? Which part?
# 我不在乎 #
I don't care
# 我就喜欢 #
I love it
# 我不在乎 #
I don't care
有人在这里! 占用中!
Someone is in here! Ocupado!
阿朱 我们在这座城市的所有盥洗室里做爱
June, we're having sex in bathrooms all across the city.
刚从一家熟食店回来
We just came from a deli.
我们给一些挫老头演了一场真人秀
We gave some old fakaktas a show.
你们为什么要在盥洗室里做爱?
Ew. Why are you having sex in bathrooms?
告诉她 阿班 用澳大利亚口音告诉她
Tell her, Ben. Tell her in the australian accent.
因为盥洗室是那么的性感
Because bathrooms are sexy.
哼!
Mmm!
我的化妆台!
My prep station!
好吧 你到底有没有和他说...
Well, did you at least tell him about--
我的男友圈? 说了 他一点都不介意
my rotation? Yeah, he's totally cool with it.
我也有情人环
I have one, too. A cycle.
好吧 只要你俩一直步调一致...
Well, good. I guess as long as you two are on the same page...
阿朱 现在你站的地方
June, some sex is about to happen
一场床戏正要上演 所以你要么加入要么出去
right where you're standing, so either get in or get out.
但是我还没化完妆 我还在化我的左眼
But I'm not finished yet. I'm still doing my left eye.
噢 天呐!
Oh, god!
# 我不在乎 #
I don't care
# 我就喜欢 #
I love it
# 我不在乎 #
I don't care
二十四小时里在十二套盥洗室里搞?
12 Bathrooms in 24 hours?
如果这都不算新纪录的话
if that's not a record,
那我真要会会能赢过我们的混蛋了
I'd like to meet the bastards who beat us.
我要在这里待一个月
You know, I'm gonna be here for a month.
我们可以 放慢节奏
We might want to... pace ourselves.
我榨干你了吗?
Oh, am I wearing you out?
你这老男人累瘫了? 要不要来点薄荷提神?
Is the old man getting tired? Do you want a peppermint?
我只是说偶尔呢
I'm just saying, at some point,
可以穿上衣服
we might have to put some clothes on
用嘴巴吃点食物
and use our mouths for food.
我知道一家脱衣舞酒吧
I know a strip club
他们家中式鸡肉沙拉做得不错
that has a great chinese chicken salad.
听起来既恶心又好吃 那就走吧
That sounds gross and delicious at the same time. Let's go.
啊!
Whoa!
噢 不 班吉b
Oh, no. Benjamin.
你的肩膀似乎脱臼了
Seems like you've got a dislocated shoulder.
我看你躺在这里
Now that I see you lying here,
才想起来我应该
I realize what I should have done--
放一片丝瓜在你的鸡鸡上
Instead of covering you with a towel,
而不是拿条毛巾把你盖起来
I should have put a small loofah over your junk.
那应该很搞笑
That would have been very funny.
我真后悔没那么做
I regret not doing that very much.
那么我们现在要送你去医院
So we just gotta get you to the hospital.
我需要你的基本资料
I'm just gonna need some info first.
- 出生日期? - 1982年4月28号
- What's your date of birth? - April 28, 1982.
是否有过敏史?
Any allergies?
除了眼前这个小尤物?
Other than this hot potato right here?
有紧急联系人吗?
An "in case of an emergency" contact?
梅琳达・圣・克莱尔 二一二
Melinda St. Claire, 2-1-2...
梅琳达・圣・克莱尔? 那是谁?
Melinda St. Claire? Who's that?
哦 她是我的情人环头一号
Oh, she's the number one girl in my cycle.
真有趣
That's so funny.
在加拿大 我们称之为炮友链
In Canada, we call it a loop.
你好 朋友
Hello, friend.
我收到你的信息了
I got your message.
# 你一定要让徘徊吗? #
do you have to let it linger?
这是什么?
What the hell is this?
我知道你嘴上说不在乎
I know you said it doesn't bother you
梅琳达・圣・克莱尔是阿班的情人环的首位
that Melinda St. Claire is number one in Ben's cycle.
但是你不能装作你不难过
But you can't pretend that you're not feeling hurt.
他是你的第一位 而你不是他的
He's your number one, and you're not his.
这太伤人了
That is jacked up.
阿朱 我已经去找我男友圈的其他人了
June, I've already moved on to other guys in my rotation.
- 我一点都不在乎 - 嘘!
- I don't really care. - Shh!
就让这首伤心情歌来为你疗伤
Just let the perfect breakup song heal your wounds.
把你的手指从我脸上拿开
Take your finger off my face.
对不起 有点过了
Sorry. That was too much.
阿朱 我不在乎阿班怎么来排他的情人环
June, I don't care how Ben ranks his cycle.
为什么你认为我同时和六个男人拍拖?
Why do you think I date six guys at a time?
就是因为这个原因呢
For exactly this reason.
厌倦了一个 就立马找下一个
One gets annoying, another one slips right in.
这就是帕特・莱利管理尼克斯队的方法
It's how Pat Riley ran the knicks.
也是我安排我性生活的规则
It's how I run my sex life.
我不信你在说实话
I don't think you're being honest with yourself.
新男人不能帮助你忘记班吉b
and another guy isn't gonna help you get over Benjamin.
你必须伤心哀悼
You have to mourn,
并且你一定要吃冰激凌
and you have to eat ice cream,
你还得做一个神龛
and you have to build a shrine.
我七年级的时候就是这么做的
That's what I did in seventh grade
那时我和艾伦・德迈亚 分手了
when me and Aaron demayo broke up.
# 你一定要让它徘徊吗? #
Do you have to let it linger?
# 你一定要吗 一定要这样吗 #
Do you have to, do you have to
# 你一定要让它徘徊吗? #
do you have to let it linger?
宝贝 我们知道你在伤心
Honey, we know you're hurting,
但这首神烦的歌我真是听够了
but enough of this gosh-Darned song.
唐纳德 不要用愤怒的口气谈论神
Donald, do not almost say "God" in anger.
这能让你感觉好起来
This will make you feel so much better.
# 你一定要让它徘徊吗? #
Do you have to let it linger?
# 一定要吗 一定要这样吗 #
Do you have to, do you have to
# 你一定要让它流逝吗 #
do you have to let it linger?
我和阿尔文老在麦霸之夜唱这首歌
My friend Alvin and I would perform that at open mic night,
然后我们会...# 毁了它 #
and we would...  crush it
他现在死了
he's dead now.
好好享用你的咖啡 承蒙詹姆斯・范德・比克的好意
Please enjoy your coffee, courtesy of James Van Der Beek.
给阿乔来杯乔家咖啡
A Cup O'Joe from a regular Joe.
希望这能赢得他们的好感
Hope this finally wins their admiration.
对我来说管用
Well, it's working for me.
我好久没喝玛奇朵了
I haven't had a macchiato in ages,
我忙死了
and I am buzzing.
詹姆斯 谢谢你的咖啡
James. Thanks for the coffee.
不客气
Hey. No problem.
我们打篮球不够人 你要来吗?
Hey, we need a fourth for basketball. You want in?
在我们等阿班的时候
Oh. You know, I really should memorize my lines
我真该去背台词
while we're waiting for Ben,
但为了你们 为了我们团队...
but for you guys, for my crew...
走吧 球员
Let's go, ballers.
太好了
Yeah. All right.
各位 不好意思我迟到了
Hey, guys. Sorry I'm late.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
我...嘿咻的时候受伤了
I, uh, injured myself during sex.
是啊
Yeah, you did.
虽然我现在痛得要死
Look, even though I'm in incredible pain
吃了药还非常晕
and quite high on prescription meds,
但没有什么能阻挡我拍完这支广告
nothing is gonna keep me from completing this commercial
为了你们...
for you guys...
我的团队
my crew.
去做事吧
Let's get to work.
我...
W--
我们这么亲近 我们...
We were so close. We were...
我们还要去打球
we were gonna play ball,
他们还要给我取昵称
and you were gonna make up a name for me,
像"范德詹詹" 或者"大回环"
like "Van der jam" Or "Hoopsta."
别担心 我来跟你打球...
Don't worry, man. I'll play ball with ya...
等我先抱抱阿班
after I hug Ben.
天哪 他真是激励人 不是吗?
Gosh. He's inspiring, you know?
他看起来身材好好
Plus, he's, like, yoked.
他家里肯定有私人健身房
He must have a home gym.
抱他的时候我得问问
I'm gonna ask him during the hug.
# 你来自七十年代 #
You're from the '70s
# 但我却是九零后贱妞 #
but I'm a '90s bitch
# 我就喜欢 #
I love it
真开心你给我打电话 克洛伊
I'm so glad you called, Chloe.
真开心你的飞机着陆了 德里克
I'm so glad you grounded your plane, Derek.
# 我就喜欢 #
I love it
你以前在盥洗室里做过吗?
you ever fool around in a bathroom before?
梅琳达时期试过
Melinda times.
什么?
What?
我参加了梅琳达俱乐部
I'm in the Melinda high club.
在我们开始前 我想让你知道
Before we get started, I just want you to know,
我的梅琳达测试呈阳性
I tested positive for Melinda.
今天是安全期吗?
Are you on birth control?
我不喜欢戴梅琳达
'Cause I don't like to wear a Melinda.
六个男人全毁了
Six guys all ruined,
那些个梅琳达在我脑海里挥之不去
and some bitch named Melinda's in my head,
都是阿班的错
and it's all Ben's fault.
团队怎么会喜欢阿班多过我呢?
How could the crew choose Ben over me?
我对他们友好
I offered them my friendship.
我为朋友两肋插刀
I would kill to be friends with me.
说真的 我...如果有人当我朋友的话
Literally, I--if somebody was friends with me,
我会捅了他们 好做自己的朋友
I would kill them so I could be friends with me.
谁把我的书从中间给撕了?
Who ripped out the middle of my book?
我需要找你聊聊
I needed to talk to you.
我努力勾搭男友圈的其他男人
I tried to hook up with the other guys in my rotation.
但是我不停地听着他们喊"梅琳达"
But I kept hearing them say "Melinda."
克洛伊 我之前就是这么说的
Chloe, this is what I was saying before.
在阿班心中不是第一位都要把你整疯了
It bugs you that you're not Ben's number one.
人生中第一次
For the first time in your life,
你开始嫉妒了
you are jealous.
拜托 我才不会嫉妒
Please. I don't get jealous.
向来是我在别人心中播下嫉妒的种子
I make jealous in other people.
我只有让别人嫉妒的份
I make other people jealous.
行吧 曾经我也是 但是你看我俩
Yeah, so did I. Now look at us.
我俩也曾辉煌过 现在呢...
We were once golden gods. Now...
现在是两只无名小卒
we're number twos.
两只蹲在浴缸里的无名小卒
Two number twos in a tub.
我买了德国的那个碟片
I bought that dvd in Germany.
怪异国度
Weird country.
克洛伊 你苦逼地坐在浴缸里
Chloe, there is a reason
而不是和男友圈五个小哥去玩
why you are sitting here in this tub
是有原因的
instead of out with your five other guys.
班吉b不仅仅是你男友圈的一位炮友
Benjamin is more than just someone in your rotation.
也许他就是呢
Maybe he is.
我的意思是 你想成为彼此的独一无二吗?
Well, I mean, do you want to be exclusive with him?
没有其他男人搅局 就和他?
No more rotation, just him?
也许我想
Maybe I do.
那么就和他说去啊
Well, then talk to him.
告诉他你是怎么想的
Tell him how you feel.
卧! 槽!
oh! Ow!
扇你是因为我不愿承认事实
That's just me being uncomfortable with the truth.
谢啦 阿朱
Thank you, June.
那些东西在你头上多久了?
How long have those been in?
一个小时了
An hour.
拿下来
Take 'em out.
班吉b・拉夫特吗?
Benjamin Lovett?
我们是美国移民局的工作人员
We're with U.S. Immigration services.
检查下你的工作签证
We need to see your work visa.
哦 好的
Uh, yeah.
保证一切材料都是合法的
I'm sure you'll find everything's current
而且在有效期内
and up to date.
对 肯定是 很好
Yep, sure is. Great.
但是你还是要被遣返
But you're still getting deported.
啥 你和我开玩笑呢?
What is this, some kind of joke?
不 先生 这是上级指示
No, sir. This comes from the very top.
我们必须把您送上前往澳洲的飞机上
We're gonna need you on a plane back to Australia.
啥 喂... 你们不能这么做
Wh--Hey, you can't do this.
为...为啥会这样?
Wh-Why is this happening?
你好
Hello.
搞定了
It's done.
多谢了朱利叶斯 我欠你个大人情
Thanks, Julius. I owe you one.
那么就像事先说好的那样
So can I take you on my brother's houseboat
我能带你去我弟的游艇吗?
like you promised?
那班吉b被遣返这事
Is there any way
有可能被撤销吗?
Benjamin's deportation can be undone?
不行 已经在处理中了
Nope. It's already been processed.
那么 免谈
Then, no.
克洛伊
Chloe.
嘿 你看见刚刚和我在一起的男的吗?
Hey, did you see that guy I was with?
他貌似是个啥保险精算人
He's something called an insurance adjuster.
太性感了
So hot.
我在考虑要不要在男友圈里给他留个位子
I'm thinking about giving him a spot in my rotation.
那阿班怎么办?
What about Ben?
他已经给我们公寓打了无数次电话了
He has called the apartment a thousand times.
你本该告诉他你真实的感觉
You were supposed to tell him how you felt,
而不是将他驱逐出境
not get him deported.
这个吗 我是想过
Well, I thought about it
然后我觉得我就想把他送回国
and I realized I felt like getting him deported.
天哪 你知道吗? 我受够了
Oh, gosh. You know what? I am done.
我再也不会给你任何恋爱建议了
I am not gonna give you any more relationship advice.
随你啊
Okay.
但是我要说最后一件事
But the last thing that I'll say
你把阿班遣送回国
is just because you got Ben deported
并不代表你对他没感觉了
doesn't mean that you'll be over him.
事实上他仍然会在你的脑海里你的心里
He's still going to be in here and in here.
他只该在姐的这里
The only place that a guy should be is here.
阿朱 我才不像你呢
June, I'm not like you.
我从不和男人夹缠不清
I don't get twisted up over guys.
我卯足经验然后向前看
I have great experiences and I move on.
我也不和男人夹缠不清
I don't get twisted up over guys either.
我就觉得你不能自私到
I just know you can't do something so selfish
毁掉别人下半生
that it affects someone for the rest of their life.
我曾经也有过这样的机会
I could've done that, too.
艾伦把我甩了之后
After Aaron broke up with me,
我勇往直前的过着自己的生活...
I was moving on with my own life...
当我发现
When I discovered
特瑞沙・费雪
that Theresa Fisher
抽烟后
was a smoker.
我本可以把举报她 让她退学
I could've busted her and gotten her expelled
这样艾伦又是我一个人的了 可我没那么做
and had Aaron all to myself, but I chose not to,
因为你不能随便毁了别人的人生
because you don't mess with people like that.
要是我当时举报她了呢?
But what if I had made a different choice?
也许艾伦和我还在约会
Maybe Aaron and I would've kept dating.
我俩仍然在一起呢 谁知道?
Maybe we'd still be together. Who knows?
这就是为啥你对这男人念念不忘啊
That's why you keep talking about this guy.
因为你觉得他是那个离你而去的人
Because you think he's the one that got away.
啥? 不 我不是这么想的
What? No, I don't think that.
现在一切都说得通了
It all makes sense now.
这就是为啥你仍对他耿耿于怀
That's why you're still obsessed
尽管这人早八百年前就把你给甩了
with some guy who dumped you a million years ago.
阿朱 你刚刚和我说那个二逼故事的时候
June, I made out with two girls
我正和这两个姑娘亲热呢
while you were telling me that stupid story.
你需要向前看啊
You need to move on with your life.
你在干嘛啊?
What are you doing?
帮你忙啊
Helping you.
也在帮你们呢
Also helping you.
要是你们想摸我胸就来吧
If you're gonna grab my boob, just grab it.
但是不要调戏我
But don't tease me.
# 我不在乎 #
I don't care
# 我就喜欢 #
I love it
# 我不在乎 #
I don't care
真是个好日子啊 不是吗?
it's a great day, isn't it?
阿班被驱逐出境了
Ben's been deported.
工作人员都慌了
The crew is in a panic.
他们现在急需的是一个领袖 一块坚石
What they need right now is a Leader, a rock.
你知道会是谁吗?
And you know who that is?
我吗?
Me?
詹姆斯 我只是开玩笑
I'm just kidding, James.
我知道是你
I know it's you.
我只是想把气氛弄轻松一点
I'm just trying to keep it light.
好的 各位 听着
All right. Listen, everyone.
我很遗憾阿班被驱逐出境
Uh, I know it's a shame about Ben being deported,
但是我想让你们知道我仍在这陪着你们
but I just wanna let you guys know that I am still here.
我不会丢下你们的
I'm not going to abandon you.
我经纪人已经和制片公司谈过了
My agent talked to the production company
让他们相信我们已经拍了足够多的镜头
and convinced them that we've already shot enough footage
能制作一支上好的广告片
to cut together a great commercial.
所以乐观说来 大家不用担心
So artistically, you guys don't need to worry.
观众会看见你们的努力
Your work will be seen.
我们应该会再拍一周的
We were supposed to shoot for another week.
还能拿到工资吗?
Will we still get paid?
为什么不呢
I don't see how.
不管怎么说 这难道不是很棒吗?
Anyway, isn't this awesome?
这周剩下的日子都放假啦!
I got us the rest of the week off!
谁想要吃寿司看场音乐会?
Who's up for sushi and a matinee?
加州卷哦!
California roll!
# 哦 啦啦啦 #
Ooh, la la la
我们不能进去 这是男厕所
we can't go in here. This is where men go.
我让我的飞行员小情人德里克
I did not get my pilot lover Derek
在最后一分钟把我们弄上飞往印第安纳的飞机
to get us on a last-Minute flight to indiana
然后来到这龙虾桶男厕所
and come to a lobster barrel bathroom
要是见不到艾伦・德迈亚那我图什么
and not confront Aaron Demayo.
艾伦・德迈亚!
Aaron demayo!
出来!
Get out here!
阿朱
June.
如果这就是他 我懂你的迷恋了 算我一个
If this is him, I get it and I am in.
- 阿朱? - 嗨 艾伦!
- June? -  Hey, Aaron!
你在这儿干吗?
What are you doing here?
阿朱还记得你以前的电话号码
June still has your old phone number memorized.
你妈说你可能在这儿
And your mom said you'd be here.
现在阿朱想和你搞清楚
Now June is gonna screw it out with you
让她明白并不是你离他而去
so she realizes that you're not the one that got away
她才能彻底放下
and finally moves on.
不!不 我...我...我不想和你搞
No! No, I...I...I don't want to screw.
我还这儿是因为
I'm here because
我那风室友想证明
my crazy roommate is trying to prove a point.
我们的关系"还没结束"
She thinks that you and I have "Unfinished business."
她和别人产生了点麻烦
She's going through a thing with a guy,
所以我努力告诉她
and I'm trying to tell her
她不能对别人无所欲为
that she can't do whatever she wants to people.
就像 当我发现特瑞沙・费雪在吸烟
Like, when I busted Theresa Fisher for smoking
我本来可以把她赶出去但是我选择不这么做
and I could've gotten her expelled but I chose not to.
哦我的天 我完全忘了特瑞沙以前吸烟
Oh, my God. I totally forgot that Theresa used to smoke.
小艾出生时
I'm surprised A.J. was
居然还能长全手指和脚趾真令人惊讶
born with all his fingers and toes
等等 谁是小艾?
Wait. Who's A.J.?
哦 抱歉 小艾是我们的儿子
Oh, sorry. A.J.'s our son.
等下 你和特瑞沙结婚了?
Wait. You and Theresa are married?
艾伦 你干吗呢这么慢?
Aaron, what is taking you so long?
小艾一直吵着要去厕所
A.J.'s insisting on going in the men's room,
你却一直不回到桌子旁
but you never came back to the table,
现在我把双胞胎留在苹果电脑和奶酪旁边了
and now I've left the twins alone with their Mac and cheese.
天哪 这也太现实了 我的天
God, this is so real. Heartland.
嗨特瑞沙 嗨我是阿朱 我们是校友
Hey, Theresa. Hi, I'm June. We went to school together.
是的 很高兴见到你 艾伦 你能帮忙带下小艾吗?
Yeah, it's nice to meet you. Aaron, can ya take A.J.?
他一直在闹他快憋死了
he keeps saying he's gonna explode.
我有事忙呢
Kind of in the middle of something here.
哦 好吧
Oh. Okay.
没关系 我来
No, I'll do it. That's fine.
不过这月末我会和姐姐一块抽抽烟
But I am going to cabo at the end of the month
我还准备喝点龙舌兰酒
with my sister, and I'm drinking Tequila.
有个小男孩在这里我就不进去了
There's a little boy in there, and that weirds me out.
艾伦 我...我不敢相信你最后和特瑞沙在一起了
Aaron, I...I can't believe you and Theresa ended up together.
他走大运了!
Livin' the dream!
我想这是命运
Guess it was fate.
是啊 要不然就是我了
Yeah. Or it was me.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
如果 我当时把特瑞沙赶出去了
Well, if, you know, I'd gotten Theresa expelled,
事情可能会完全不同
things might've turned out differently.
也许我们会继续约会
You know, maybe you and I would've kept on dating.
也许我们现在还在约会
Maybe we'd still be dating.
谁知道呢? 也许今天是我在那个隔间里
Who knows? Maybe I'd be the one in there in the stall,
帮小艾把尿
helping A.J. Go.
嗨 进来 亲爱的! 别客气!
Hey, get in here, honey! Knock yourself out!
阿朱 你所描绘的这幅画面...
June, this picture that you're painting...
你真的想要吗?
do you really want it?
你真的想和这个人还有那个孩子
Do you really wanna live here
还有这些龙虾在这儿?
with this guy and that baby and these lobsters?
我...
W-Well, I...
还是说因为这男人弃你而去
or did you just get hung up on the idea
你就对这个念头耿耿于怀?
because you thought this guy was the one who got away?
你说的对
You're right.
我在说什么? 我...我不想这样生活
What am I talking about? I...I don't want this.
我想要这种
I want this.
哦 我懂了
Oh, I knew it.
阿朱 我亲那些女孩
June, I kissed those girls
是为了说明你的故事有多无聊
to illustrate how Boring your story was.
- 如果让你误会了 我... - 不! 不是!
- If I misled you in some way, I... - No! No!
我想要以你为代表的...
I want what you represent...
我在纽约的生活 那种我已经拥有的生活
my life in New York, the life that I already have.
看吧? 我说过你迈了一大步 你终于搞明白了
See? I told you. You make a big move and you get clarity.
你只需要把艾伦・德迈亚从你的模式中踢出去
You just had to get Aaron demayo out of your system,
就像我对待班吉b
the same way I had to do with Benjamin.
哦 班吉b是刚被我驱逐出境的人
Oh, Benjamin is this guy that I got deported.
说来话长了
It's a really long story,
不过我现在就告诉你
but I'll tell you about it right now.
我们最终在同一座城市里
We were finally going to be in the same city
待了很长一段时间
for a long stretch of time,
所以我们决定尽可能在每一个盥洗室里做爱
so we decided to have sex in bathrooms everywhere we could.
在我的公寓里 黛安・索耶的更衣室里
We did it in my apartment, Diane Sawyer's dressing room,
还有房车里....
an R.V...
哦 我的天 我在说什么?
Oh, my God. What am I doing?
为什么我会谈起
Why am I talking about
八百年前发生的事?
something that happened a million years ago?
是昨天刚发生
That was yesterday.
非常正确! 为什么还没忘掉?
Exactly! Why haven't I moved on?
谁能帮我把这些纸巾全递过来?
Can someone hand me all the paper towels?
你还没有开始新的生活因为
You haven't moved on yet because he's still
他依然在你的脑海里你的心里
in there and there,
虽然他不在这儿
even though he's not in there.
我还是忘不了他
I'm not over him.
占用中
Occupied.
我是机长
It's your captain.
嗨 我是...我是德里克
Hey, I'm...I'm Derek.
在克洛伊的男友圈里排第三
Uh, number three in Chloe's rotation.
有你的电话
You have a phone call.
- 喂? - 对不起 很抱歉
- Hello? - Sorry. I'm sorry.
要命克洛伊?! 是你把我驱逐出境的?!
What the hell, Chloe?! you had me deported?!
我一年内都不能再回美国!
I can't come back to the states for a year!
好吧! 你去妈的!
Fine! Screw you!
对不起 我...
Sorry. I'm...
我正在努力向你道歉 好不好?
this is me trying to apologize. All right?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你为什么这么做?
Why'd you do it?
我...想
I... had to.
你说过梅琳达在你情人里排第一 我有点嫉妒
You said Melinda was your number one, and I got jealous.
你为什么不早说?
Why didn't you say anything?
你可以和我谈谈你的感受而不是毁了我的生活
You could've talked to be about it instead of ruining my life.
因为我不想让你知道
Because I don't want to talk to you about this.
我怕我想要这样生活
I don't want to want this.
我是说 也许等我们老了 一起走在路上
I mean, maybe someday down the road, when we're old...
除非你年轻不老
unless you don't age well.
我预感你的脖子上会长满赘肉
I have a feeling your neck could get gross.
在乎一个人是件好事
You know, it's okay to care about somebody.
我知道 所以打给你
I know, and that's why I'm calling you.
很抱歉把你驱逐出境
I'm sorry that I did this to you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
但是为了自己我不后悔这么做
But I'm not sorry I did this for me.
我还没准备好过这样的生活
I'm not ready for all this.
我明白
I get it.
或许某天会的
Maybe someday.
你不会忘了我的 对不?
You're gonna hang up on me now, aren't you?
是的
Yes.
嗨
Hey.
- 怎么样了? - 很好
- How'd it go? - Good.
那么我们干杯
Well, cheers to us.
为我们的生活更进一步
To moving on.
我终于放下了甩了我的人
I finally got over the one who got away,
而你...甩了放不下的人
and you... got away.
我跟你说过爱上一个人很傻
I told you it's dumb to get caught up with one guy.
就像得了幽闭症
It's claustrophobic.
就像住在一个巨大的漂亮公寓
It's like living in a big beautiful apartment
却只在厕所里转悠
and only hanging out in the bathroom.
这是干吗?
What's going on?
追忆初中时光
Back in junior high,
我是我最喜欢的伤心情歌
this was my favorite post-breakup empowerment song.
# 生活要悉心聆听 #
Listen as your day unfolds
# 向未知的明天挑战 #
challenge what the future holds
＃努力向天空保持昂首姿态　＃
try and keep your head up to the sky
＃ 你必须　＃
you gotta be
＃ 你必须变得厉害 你必须变的勇敢 #
You gotta be bad, you gotta be bold
# 你必须... #
you gotta be...
巨大的进步
Big move.
好吧 谢谢
Yep. Thanks.
清醒
力量
兼容
牛蛙太阳眼镜
您双眼的盥洗室